<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Brush descriptions-->
<string name="descr_line"><![CDATA[
<h1> Line </h1>

<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
This is a classic stroke without any modifications.
</p>
<p><em>Fill mode</em> : Yes.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_scrawl"><![CDATA[
<h1>Scrawl</h1>

<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
This is a random stroke. Your stroke is decomposed in different segments and each one are deformed randomly.
</p>
<h3> Options </h3>

<p>
<em>Noise</em> : amplitude of a deformation in a segment.
</p>
<p>
<em>Details</em> : number of deformations for one segment.
</p>
<p>
<em>Flow</em> : segment frequency.
Short flow means a short and more deformed segment for the same details value.
</p>

<p><em>Fill mode</em> : Yes.</p>
]]></string>

<string name="descr_splatter"><![CDATA[
<h1>Splatter</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
This is a dripping stroke. This is composed of a main stroke and some drips. They are both
with
a thickness inversely proportional to the stroke speed.
</p>
<h3>Options</h3>

<p>
<em>Size</em>
: size parameter for the drips and the main stroke.
</p>
<p>
<em>Drips</em>
: number of drips.
</p>

<p><em>Fill mode</em>
: No.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_ribbon"><![CDATA[
<h1>Ribbon</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
This stroke is composed of several ribbons. Caution : a very long stroke (without remove your finger) can reduce the performances.
</p>
<h3>Options</h3>

<p>
<em>Gravity</em>
: gravity parameter.
</p>
<p>
<em>Friction</em>
: friction parameter.
</p>
<p>
<em>Spacing</em>
: the frequency at which a ribbon is added.
</p>

<p><em>Fill mode</em> : Yes.</p>

]]></string>
<string name="descr_xshape"><![CDATA[
<h1>XSphape</h1>

<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
This is a randomly broken line stroke. Your stroke is decomposed in different segments and each one is composed of random straight lines.
</p>
<h3> Options </h3>

<p>
<em>Noise</em> : length parameter of the straight lines.
</p>
<p>
<em>Details</em> : number of straight lines for one segment.
</p>
<p>
<em>Flow</em> : segment frequency.
Short flow means  a short and more deformed segment for the same details value.
</p>

<p><em>Fill mode</em> : Yes.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_paint_brush"><![CDATA[
<h1> Paintbrush </h1>

<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
This is emulation of a "real brush" with few bristles.
</p>
<h3> Options </h3>

<p>
<em>Bristles</em> : number of bristles. Caution : a high number can reduce the performances without specially looking better.
</p>

<p><em>Fill mode</em> : No.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_basic_shapes"><![CDATA[
<h1> Basic shape </h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
This brush is made of different basic shapes : Box, Circle and Triangle.
You can chose one kind of shape or all of them in a random pattern.
The size of a shape is proportional to the stroke speed.
</p>
<p><em>Fill mode</em> : Yes.</p>
]]></string>

<string name="descr_ball"><![CDATA[
<h1> Ball </h1>

<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
This brush create "balls". One ball is a group of concentric circles.
</p>
<h3> Options </h3>

<p>
<em>Size</em> : radius size parameter.
</p>
<p>
<em>Radius</em> : number of concentric circles for one ball.
</p>
<p>
<em>Flow</em> : frequency of balls.
</p>

<p><em>Fill mode</em> : Yes.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_straight_line"><![CDATA[
<h2> Straight Line </h2>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
Each stroke will produce a single straight line.
If snapping is enabled, the beginning of the line will be the closest extremity of previous lines if it is not too far.
</p>
<p><em>Fill mode</em> : No.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_web_brush"><![CDATA[
<h1>Web brush</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
This stroke is composed of small straight lines.
If an extremity of one line is close enough to the extremity of an other line (from this
stroke
or previous ones),
there will be an extra line between these two extremities.
</p>
<h3>Options</h3>
<p>
<em>Max Dist</em>
: Maximal distance between two extremities to have an extra line.
</p>
<p><em>Fill mode</em>
: No.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_sketch_brush">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Sketch brush</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
Variation of the web brush (see web brush) with shorter extra lines.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_xshape_v2">
<![CDATA[
<h1>XShape V2</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
This is an other randomly broken lines stroke with a different algorithm than the first XShape brush.
</p>
<h3>Options</h3>
<p>
<em>Noise</em>
: randomness of the broken lines.
</p>
<p><em>Fill mode</em>
: Yes.</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_brushes">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Brushes</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
Drawchemy possess several brushes and each brush has its own effect.
Most of them have parameters that can be tweak (see Settings). Some do not support the fill mode (see Fill).
</p>
]]></string>
</resources>