<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string name="descr_load">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Load</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Load a image from your device and use it as background.
    The image is automatically scaled and rotated to fit your canvas for the best.
    Your previous canvas is completely erased. You can not undo a load operation.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_share">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Share</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Save your canvas in PNG format and allow you to share it with an other application from your device.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_save">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Save</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Save your canvas in PNG format. The location will be in the DRAWCHEMY folder inside your Picture folder.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_clear">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Clear</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Clear your canvas. The background color will be the secondary color (see Colors).
    You can not undo a clear operation.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_zoom_pan">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Pan and zoom</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Allow you to pan the canvas with one finger or zoom with two.
    To quit the pan and zoom, click on a icon of the Action Bar (top bar) or the bottom bar,
    even the pan and zoom icon.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_reset_view">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Reset view</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Reset the scale and the position of the canvas (see Pan and zoom).
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_undo">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Undo</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Cancel the last stroke. You can undo up to 5 strokes by default.
    You can increase or decrease this number in the extra settings.
    If you change this number, it will be effective after your next stroke.
    The memory footprint of the application will increase with the number of possible undos.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_hide">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Hide/Show User Interface</h1>
<h3> Description </h3>
<p>
    Click on the logo to remove the user interface. The logo will still show up semi-transparent.
    Click again to get back the user interface.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_settings">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Settings</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
   Display a user interface to parameterize the current brush.
</p>
]]></string>
<string name="descr_extra">
<![CDATA[
<h1>Extra settings</h1>
<h3>Description</h3>
<p>
   Display a user interface to parameterize the number of possible undos (see Undo) and the kaleidoscope (see Kaleidoscope).
</p>
]]></string>
    <string name="descr_help">
        <![CDATA[
<p>
  <strong>Click on an item in the menu to get its description.</strong>
</p>
]]></string>
</resources>